to do i'm seeing people say things like i have to get off of social media to protect my mental
health which i'm just like again y'all in this fucking mental health and if you're not breaking
down and you're not hurting you're not living y'all think that preserving your happiness
is like some sort of revolution but which what i but i don't think that that's really a thing
when there's actually sadness and incredible degradation happening i understand that some
people actually have clinical issues they have actual clinical diagnoses that can turn very
dangerous that i understand and they don't have support systems that i understand but some of y'all
are just weak you're weak and you really just don't want to be uncomfortable
and you don't want to hurt and you call it mental health our eyes are being opened
and your heart should be opening at the same time